&gt;&gt; Good morning.
&gt;&gt; 早上好
I'm Chelsea Pugh and I'm an
我叫 Chelsea Pugh
engineer on the Safari team.
是 Safari 团队的一名工程师
Welcome to session 225, What's
欢迎来到今天的研讨会
New in Safari View Controller.
和我们一起探讨 SafariViewController 的新功能
Safari View Controller has a
SafariViewController 在 iOS 11
bunch of improvements on iOS 11.
系统中有了许多新的提升
It also has new APIs that were
包括一些由
inspired by feedback that we got
开发者提供的反馈所
from developers.
启发的新 API
I'm really excited to share some
今天能和大家分享
of Safari View Controller's new
SafariViewContrller 的新功能
abilities with you today.
我感到很激动
One main use case of displaying
iOS 上网页内容所展示的一大用例
web content on iOS is to allow
便是允许用户在
users to browse the web in your
App 中浏览
app.
网页
You might be displaying a list
你可能会放上一些可以将
of links that could lead the
用户引导到新闻文章的
user to news articles or maybe
链接或者
your displaying a list of links
将用户引导至
that could lead to information
网上不同话题信息的
of different topics on the web.
链接
It could, these links could your
这些链接可以将
user anywhere on the web, and
你的用户引导至网络中的任何一个地方
you don't expect to know where
但你却不能提前
they'll end up ahead of time.
知晓
How many of you are doing
有多少人在你们的 App
something like this in your app?
中使用这种方法呢
All right, there's a few of you
嗯 看起来人数
out there.
挺多的
You're in the right place.
你们找对方式了
Another main reason that you'd
你们想在 iOS 上展示
want to display web content on
网页内容的另一个原因是
iOS is to allow your users to
网页内容为了让你的客户
get authenticated with a
授权第三方服务 允许
third-party service so that it's
你在你的 App 中使用
data can be used in your app.
该第三方服务的数据
How many of you do something
有多少人在 App 里面使用了
like that in your app?
这种方式呢
You're also in the right place.
你们同样做出了正确选择
And for those of you that are
我想问一下 在你们
providing those experiences to
当中
your user, how many of you are
有多少人已经
already using Safari View
开始使用
Controller?
SafariViewController
Great. If you're already using
很好 如果你已经在使用
some improvements to share with
那今天我们将会与你分享
you today that will make Safari
SafariViewController 一些能够
View Controller an even better
为你的用户提供更好体验
experience for your users.
的更新
If you aren't using Safari View
如果你还没有开始使用 SafariViewController
Controller but you're providing
但你在为用户提供这些体验的一种，
one of those experiences, listen
那你可要认真
up.
听讲了
The new APIs that we're going to
我们今天将要讨论的新版 API
talk about today were inspired
是由你们的反馈所启发而来的
by feedback from you, and we
我想你们
think you'll really like to hear
会很希望能了解
about it.
它们
Today I'm going to cover
今天 我将会谈及
displaying web content on iOS.
在 iOS 上展示网页内容
Then I'll talk about how to
之后 我将会介绍一下
really match your app's style
如何用 SafariViewController
using Safari View Controller.
来统一你的 App 风格
I'll then talk about some
之后 我还将谈一谈
improvements to Safari View
iOS 11 上 SafariViewerController
Controller on iOS 11.
的一些提升
Then I'll discuss the new APIs
同时 还会再讨论一下 SafariViewController
that have been added to Safari
上新增的 API 这些 API
View Controller to really tailor
将调整 SafariaViewController
it to fit your app's use case.
使之符合你的 App 用例
First, displaying web content.
首先 展示网页内容
There are a couple of different
展示网页内容有几种不同的方式
ways, but today I'm going to
今天我将会讨论其中
talk about two of those, using
两种
SFSafariViewController and using
使用 SFSafariViewController 和
WKWebView.
使用 WKWebView
To start off, let's talk about
让我们先从 SFSafariViewCongroller
SFSafariViewController.
开始
If you don't know where your
如果你不知道你的用户们
user will be going on the web,
最终会访问哪些网页
Safari View Controller is really
那么 SafariViewController
a good thing for you to use.
是个不错的选择
It gives you standard browsing
它能为你提供标准的浏览
features so you don't need to
功能 使你不再
worry about implementing an
担心该如何实现一个 in-app
in-app web browser.
的网页浏览器
With just a couple lines of
只需要几行代码
code, you get an in-app web
你就能拥有一个 in-app 浏览器
browser with all of the features
这个浏览器将会具备所有
that your users know and love
被你的用户了解并热爱
from Safari in your app.
的 Safari 功能
Safari View Controller is also
在用户授权第三方服务
great for getting users
方面 SafariViewController
authenticated to a third-party
的表现
service.
也值得称赞
It has the security that users
它既有用户登录时所需要
need while logging in and it has
的安全性 也能提供
features that can help them get
帮助用户快速登录
logged in quickly.
的功能
One main example is Password
比如
AutoFill.
密码自动填充功能
They can quickly fill their
这个功能可以快速填充
saved passwords from Safari and
用户在 Safari 中保存的密码
log in with a tap of a button.
使用户可以一键登录
Now let's talk about WKWebView.
接下来 WKWebView
If you don't know the web, or if
如果你不知道网页内容 或者
you know the content that you'll
你事先已经知道
be displaying to users ahead of
所要展示的内容
time, or you even have control
或者你甚至能够控制
over the web content, WKWebView
网页内容 WKWebView
might be right for you.
都将适用于你
It allows you to manipulate the
它允许你通过 Javascript
DOM using Javascript.
控制 DOM
You can also customize
你还可以通过屏蔽或
navigations by blocking or
修改导航栏来
modifying them.
加以定制
It's a view of web content, so
这是网页内容的一种视图 所以
you can add your own native UI
你可以在网页内容上加上
around the web content.
你自己的原生 UI
This is great if part of your
如果你的 App 的 UI 有
app's UI is implemented using
一些是通过网页技术应用的
web technologies.
那这种方式就很好
The web content can blend
网页内容可以与你的
seamlessly in with your app's
本地 UI 无缝契合
native UI, so users don't even
使你的用户甚至无需知晓
need to know that they're
他们正在
interacting with web content.
与网页内容沟通
But let's get back to Safari
让我们回到 SafariViewController 上来
View Controller since I think
因为我想这才是
that's why you're all here.
你们参加这次会议的原因
Safari View Controller makes
SafariViewController 使
in-app web browsing easy.
in-app 网页浏览变得容易
As I mentioned before, with just
正如我之前所说到的 只需要几行
a couple lines of code, you've
代码 你的 App 就
got a fully featured web browser
能拥有一个功能齐全
within your app.
的浏览器
It provides a secure and safe
它能为用户提供
browsing experience for users.
安全的浏览体验
Let me tell you about a few of
让我来展示一下 SafariViewController
the security features you get
能为你提供的一些
with Safari View Controller.
安全功能
First, process separation.
首先 程序隔离
There's your app's content and
这个是你的 App 的内容
then there's web content.
这个是网页内容
Safari View Controller is in a
SafariViewController 和你的 App
separate process from your app.
是相互独立的进程
This means that anything that
这代表着用户在网页上所
the user does on the web won't
做的任何操作都不会
have an effect on your app's
影响到你 App
content.
的内容
If they browse to malicious web
就算你浏览的是一个恶意网页
page it won't be able to affect
也不会影响到你 App
your app's data.
的数据
You get out of the business of
你将不必再担心
taking care of user security on
网页上的用户安全
the web because Safari View
因为 SafariViewController 将
Controller will take care of
为你解决这个
that for you.
问题
It provides critical security
它提供了关键的
features.
安全功能
Let's talk about a couple of
让我们来讨论一下其中
those.
几个
The lock icon here indicates to
这个锁的图标代表
the user that they're browsing
用户正在通过一个
over a secure connection.
安全链接浏览网页
This is a really important
这个功能在浏览器
feature in a browser.
中是十分重要的
And you don't need to worry
如果你用的是 SafariViewController
about implementing it if you use
那么你就不用担心如何
Safari View Controller for your
将这个功能
in-app web browser.
应用到你的 in-app 浏览器中
Safari View Controller will also
当用户试图浏览
warn users if they might be
可能会盗取他们个人信息
trying to navigate to a page
的网站时 SafariViewController
that's going to try to steal
会向他们发出
their information.
警告
This page is trying to imitate
这个网页正在试图模仿
example.com to get my
example.com 来获得我的
information.
信息
And you get features from
同时你也可以拥有
Safari.
Safari 的功能
Let me just highlight a few of
让我来强调几个
the features that you'll get
SafariViewController 上的
with Safari View Controller.
功能
You get AutoFill of passwords,
密码自动填充
contact info, and credit cards.
联系人信息 信用卡
Users can quickly fill out forms
用户可以在网上快速地
on the web.
填完一张表格
Reader is an awesome feature for
Reader 是一个用于
decluttering articles on the
整理网络文章的
web.
很棒的功能
Our users of this feature love
使用这个功能的用户都
it, and they'll love getting to
很爱这个功能 如果能在你们的 App
use it in your app.
中使用这个功能 他们应该也会很喜欢
ApplePay on the web can help
网页的 ApplePay 可以让你的
users quickly make payments
用户在你的 App 中购物时
while shopping on the web within
快速
your app.
付款
And users get access to the
用户同时还可以
Share Sheet that they get
使用可以前往系统其他 App 的
elsewhere on the system.
Share Sheet
They get access to some standard
他们不仅可以使用一些
system activities that they
他们想要用的标准系统活动
might want to perform, as well
也可以获取
as any third-party extensions
Safari 上的第三方
that they have access to in
扩展
Safari.
服务
And they get content blocker
还能拥有 Safari
extensions that they'd have in
上的内容屏蔽器的
Safari.
扩展
This means they won't be
这意味着他们将
confused about why their
不再困惑为什么他们的
ad-blocker isn't working when
广告屏蔽器在你的 App
browsing the web in your app.
中浏览网页时失效了
And there are so many other
选择 SafariViewController
features that you get by
作为你的 in-app 浏览器
implementing Safari View
还能为你提供
Controller as your in-app web
许多其他的
browser.
功能
Now, I'd like to talk to you
现在 我想要和你们谈谈
about how you can better match
如何更好的让
your app's style with Safari
iOS 11 版的 SafariViewController
View Controller on iOS 11.
与你 App 的风格相匹配
There are a couple of new ways.
实现这个效果有几种新的方式
First, it has a new look.
首先 SafariViewController 有新的外观
If you've seen Safari View
如果你见过 iOS 11 之前版本的
Controller prior to iOS 11 you
SafariViewController
might have noticed that it
你可能会发现 它长得和 Safari
looked a lot like Safari.
很像
Let's take a look on iOS 11.
让我们来看看 iOS 11 版的 SafariViewController
It looks more like an in-app web
它看起来更像一个
browser so users don't feel like
in-app 浏览器 这样子用户就不会觉得
they've jumped out of your app.
他们脱离了你的 App
This is the design on iPhone.
这是在 iPhone 上的设计
It looks great on iPad too.
在 iPad 上看起来也不错
Now I want to talk to you about
接下来要说的是如何
customizing the color of Safari
自定义 SafariViewController 的颜色
View Controller so that it fits
使它符合
with your app's color scheme.
你 App 的配色
The ability to customize Safari
调整 SafariViewController 颜色
View Controller's color was
的这一功能 其实在 iOS 11 之前的版本
available prior to iOS 11, but
中就已经存在了
we've made an improvement that I
但是我们在这方面做了一个我迫不及待
really want you to know about.
想与你们分享的升级
First, let's recap the
先让我们来重新演示一遍
customizations.
个性化的流程
This is a default Safari View
这是一个默认状态的
Controller.
SafariViewController
It has the same color scheme as
它有着和 Safari 一样的配色
Safari, blue and white.
蓝色和白色
But let's say my app has a
假设我的 App 的配色
different color scheme, black
和这个不同 是黑色和
and aqua.
青色
Here I started using my app's
这里我开始将我的 App
color scheme in Safari View
的配色应用到
Controller.
SafariViewControlelr 中
So, when I present Safari View
通过这种方式 当我向我的
Controller to my users it
用户们展示 SafariViewController 时
doesn't feel like they've left
他们并不会觉得他们离开了
my app.
我的 App
And it's a really seamless
这绝对是一种
experience.
无缝体验
You can set these colors by
你可以通过修改 SFSafariViewController 上
modifying properties on
的属性来
SFSafariViewController.
设定这些颜色
To set the color of bars
如果要设置围绕着网页内容
surrounding web content you can
的栏的颜色 你可以使用
use preferredBarTintColor.
preferredBarTintColor
And to set the color of the
你也可以通过
controls shown here, you can use
preferredControlTintColor 来
preferredControlTintColor.
设置这里显示的控制器的颜色
Now let me tell you about an
我想和你介绍 iOS 11
improvement to
中 preferredBarTintColor 的
preferredBarTintColor on iOS 11.
一大升级
This is my app.
这是我的 App
I'm using my favorite shade of
我用的是我最喜欢的红色来作为
red for its bar color.
栏的颜色
Here's what it would look like
这是我在 iOS 10 版的
if I set that exact same shade
SafariViewController 中
of red to Safari View
将栏的颜色
Controller's bar color on iOS
设为完全相同的红色
10.
的样子
As you can see, they don't quite
正如你们所能看到的 它们并不是
match up.
很一致
And it doesn't feel exactly like
这个感觉也不是很像
my app.
我的 App
It looks great, but it's not as
它看起来很不错 但是它没有做到
close as it could be.
尽善尽美
Let's take a look on iOS 11.
让我们来看看 iOS 11 版是怎样的
Now, the bar colors match up.
现在 栏的颜色吻合了
It's just as if I was setting
看起来就像我在
the bar color on a standard UI
标准 UINavigationBar 或者 UIToolbar
navigation bar or UI toolbar.
上对栏的颜色进行了设置
So, it looks really great and it
所以它看起来很棒而且
fits well within my app.
和我的 App 相符
Now, I'm delighted to invite my
接下来 我很高兴的邀请我的同事
colleague Louie Livon-Bemel to
Louie Livon-Bemel 上台来
the stage to show you just how
向你们展示
easy it is to get Safari View
让 SafariViewControleller
Controller matching your app's
与你的 App 风格相符是一件
style.
多么简单的事情
Thank you.
谢谢
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Thanks, Chelsea.
&gt;&gt; 谢谢 Chelsea
Hi, I'm Louie, I'm an engineer
大家好 我叫 Louie
on the Safari team, and I'm
是 Safari  团队的一名工程师
really excited to show you just
今天很高兴能向你们展示
how easy it is to customize
将 SafariViewController
Safari View Controller to match
与你们的 App 风格相匹配
your app style.
是多么简单的一件事
I'm working on an all new
我正在开发我的 App
version of my app, Pizza Finder.
Pizza Finder 的新版本
It's the best app for finding
这个 App 是当你在专心工作或者正在观看
great pizza near you when you're
一个样片时 为你
working on or even watching a
找到周围最好吃的披萨店
demo.
的不二之选
Like many of your apps, this app
和许多你们的 App 一样
uses a standard UI Navigation
这个 App 使用的是标准
Controller.
UINavigationCotnroller
I've got a list of pizza places
这里有披萨店的列表
here, and when I tap one, a new
当我点击其中一个时
view comes in from right to left
会有一个新的视图从右到左出现
with more details.
以展示更多细节
The default presentation of
SafariViewController 的默认
Safari View Controller is a lot
展示方式和这个
like this.
很类似
When I tap on the website,
当我点击一个网址时
Safari View Controller came in
SafariViewController 会像
from right to left just like a
一个 UINavigationController
UI Navigation Controller.
一样从右到左出现
Users can even interactively
用户甚至可以在浏览完
edge swipe back when they're
之后 交互式的
done browsing.
滑动返回
So, this is great.
这个操作挺棒的
I have a very standard UI here
这里我有一个非常标准的 UI
that my users are used to from
我的用户们应该能在
Safari and any other app that's
Safari 和系统中
using Safari View Controller on
其他使用 SafariViewController
the system.
的应用中能经常见到它
Users even get really advanced
用户们甚至还能使用一些
features like in the Share Sheet
很高级的功能比如他们可以通过 ShareSheet
all the activities they're used
获得他们在 Safari 及其他
to from Safari and the powerful
强大的第三方扩展
third-party extensions that
上常用的
they're used to using.
服务
However, this isn't perfect.
然而 这并不是完美的
It sort of feels like you're
它让人觉得
somewhere else.
他们是使用另外一个 App
You might be in another app or
也许你正在使用另一个 App 或者
somewhere else on the system or
正在系统的另一个地方 或者
somewhere else in my app, it
在我的 App 中的某处
doesn't, it's not clear that
它并没有明确的表现出
you're still within Pizza
你现在还在使用
Finder.
Pizza Finder
So, I want to show you how to
所以 我想要向你们展示
improve this.
如何改善这一点
Here's where I'm presenting
这里是我在我的 App
Safari View Controller in my
中展示 SafariViewController
app.
的地方
It's really simple.
操作很简单
All you need to do to adopt
你只需要做两件事情
Safari View Controller is do two
就能使用
things.
SafariViewControlelr
The first one, is create a
第一件就是用你想要
Safari View Controller using the
导向的 URL 创造
URL that you want to lead to.
一个 SafariViewController
The second thing you need to do
第二件就是
is present it.
展示它
And that's it, that's how you
大功告成这就是你采用
adapt Safari View Controller.
SafariViewController 的过程
But let's make a few changes.
但是 让我们来做点改变
So, I've done two different
在这里
things here.
我修改了两个地方
The first one is setting the
第一个是将
preferredBarTintColor to the
preferredBarTintColor 设置为
same bar color I'm using
与我 App 中其他地方
elsewhere in my app.
的颜色一致
In this case it's that orangish
在这个例子里是
red color.
橙红色的
Second thing I'm doing is
第二个变化是我将
setting the
preferredControlTintColor
preferredControlTintColor to the
设为
same control color I'm using
与我 App 中其他控制颜色一致
elsewhere in my app, in this
也就是
case that's white.
白色
So, I'll rebuild and I'll show
接下来我将会重建并
you how these changes affect
向你们展示这些变化对
Pizza Finder.
Pizza Finder 的影响
Now when I look at a pizza
现在 当我查看一家披萨店
place, and go to their website,
并浏览他们的网站时
Safari View Controller matches
SafariViewController 与我的
my app's branding and it's
App 的整体风格相符
really obvious that I'm still
让我明显感觉到我当前还是
within Pizza Finder.
在 Pizza Finder 里
It doesn't feel like I'm
并没有给我一种
somewhere else.
离开了这个应用的感觉
That's just how easy it is to
看 个性化 SafariViewController
customize Safari View Controller
使它符合你的 App 风格 并
to match your app style and get
让你的 App 品牌化
your app's branding.
是多么的简单
Thank you so much, and I'll now
十分感谢大家 接下来
hand it back over to Chelsea.
我将会把舞台交给 Chelsea
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Thanks, Louie.
&gt;&gt; 谢谢 Louie
Louie just showed you how easy
Louie 刚刚向你们展示了
it is to get his app's branding
用 SafariViewController
in Safari View Controller.
将他的 App 品牌化是多么的简单
With just a couple lines of
他仅仅用了几行代码
code, he had Safari View
就让 SafariViewController
Controller up and running with
采用了他的 App
his app's color scheme.
配色
We can't wait to see how good
我们等不及想看看
Safari View Controller's color
你们 App 上的
schemes look on your app.
SafariViewController 的配色将会是怎么样的
Now, I'd like to talk to you
接着 我会谈到
about some improvements that
我们在 iOS 11 版的
we've made to Safari View
SafariViewControlelr 上所做
Controller on iOS 11.
的一些升级
There are five key improvements
我将会讲到
that I'm going to talk about.
五个关键的升级
You may have heard about the new
你们可能已经听说过
feature on iOS 11, Drag and
iOS 11 的新功能
Drop.
拖放
I'm excited to let you know that
我很激动的宣布 iOS 11 版的
on iOS 11, Safari View
SafariViewController 将
Controller has Drag and Drop out
实现应用内
of the box.
拖放的功能
Users can easily drag URLs out
用户们可以随意的将 URLs
of Safari View Controller into
从 SafariViewController 中拖出
other apps.
放到其他应用中
Now I'd like to talk to you
接下来要介绍的是
about some improvements to how
我们对 SafariViewController
Status Bar styling works in
中状态栏样式
Safari View Controller.
所做的升级
When presenting Safari View
当在某些 App 中使用
Controller in some apps, the
SafariViewController 时
Status Bar can become difficult
状态栏会变得
to read.
难以识别
It's hard to even notice here,
甚至像这里 深紫色的状态栏
but I have a dark purple bar,
和黑色
with a black Status Bar text on
的状态栏字体
top, and it's illegible.
还是无法识别到状态栏
Ideally, you'd want white Status
理想中 你想要的是一个白色的
Bar text so that the user can
状态栏文字 让用户可以更
easily read the Status Bar, but
轻松地阅读状态栏
if you just hard code a specific
但是 就算你把状态栏
Status Bar style, you're not
的样式写死了 你也
fully fixing the problem.
没有完全解决这个问题
Other views can be presented in
SafariViewController 上
Safari View Controller such as
也可以显示其他视图 比如
the Messages extension, or a
短信 或者
full-screen video.
全屏视频
Here the user is sharing to
你可以看到 这里用户正在
Messages so the white Status Bar
将内容分享至短信 而被你写死
style that's been hard coded is
的状态栏样式在白色的短信
illegible over the white bar of
视图上也
the Messages view.
变得无法识别
The bottom line is that other
根本原因是因为
views can be presented in Safari
SafariViewController
View Controller.
上可以展示其他视图
Safari View Controller has
当其他
improvements to better adapt the
视图在 iOS 11 系统中出现时
Status Bar style when other
SafariViewController
views are presented on iOS 11.
能够更好的适应状态栏样式
In order to allow this to work,
为了实现这个功能
you'll want to use
你将会需要使用
UIViewController-based Status
以 UIViewController 为基础的
Bar appearance.
状态栏样式
This has been the recommendation
从 iOS 7 开始我们
for all apps since iOS 7.
便推荐所有 App 使用这个样式
To do this, you can set
你可以通过
UIViewControllerBased
将你 App 的
StatusBarAppearance to yes in
Info.plist 中的 UIViewCoontrollerBased
your app's Info.plist.
StatusBarAppearance 设为 yes
This will ensure that the Status
这能保证你的状态栏
Bar remains legible even when
清晰可见
other views are presented in
即使其他视图
Safari View Controller.
出现在 SafariViewController 上也没关系
Now I'd like to tell you about
现在我将会和你们
another improvement, but it
分享另一个升级
requires a bit of background.
但我需要一点点背景信息
So, I'd like to explain a
我想通过
scenario in Safari to start.
Safari 中的一个场景来作为切入
A common experience on the web
网络上的一个最常见的
is checkout with a third-party
体验就是使用
service.
第三方服务支付
Here I have a page that's asking
这个页面要求我
me to checkout using Example
用 Example 支付
Checkout.
来付款
When I tap buy now in Safari, a
当我在 Safari 上点击 立即购买时
new tab is opened and I'm able
就打开了一个新的界面 我就能
to complete my payment.
完成付款
When I tap Buy Now on Example
当我点击 Example Checkout 中
Checkout, I -- and complete my
的现在付款 并完成
payment, the tab that was opened
我的付款操作时 之前打开的界面
is closed and I'm back on the
便关闭了 我回到了
store site that I was on.
我刚刚所在的商店页面
And the store knows that I've
同时 商店也知道
completed my payment.
我已经完成了我的付款
This is an example of what
这就是当一个网页
happens when a webpage calls
要求 window.open 以及
window.open and subsequently
随后 window.close 的过程
calls window.close.
的例子
It previously wasn't supported
之前的 SafariViewController 并不
in Safari View Controller
支持这一功能
because Safari View Controller
因为它没有
doesn't have tabs.
界面
But on iOS 11 Safari View
但是 iOS 11 版的 SafariViewController
Controller supports window.open.
支持 window.open 了
[applause] It's pretty great,
是的 这
yeah.
很棒
The way that this now works is
在 SafariViewController 上
in Safari View Controller when I
的操作方式是这样子的
tap Buy Now a new, I've
当我点击现在购买时 我是向前
navigated forward instead of
巡览而不是
opening a new tab.
打开一个新的界面
Once I've completed my payment
我完成支付之后
after tapping Buy Now, I'm
我则是向后巡览回到
navigated back to the page, the
之前我所在界面的域名
domain I was on and the page
这个页面也知道
knows that I've completed my
我已经完成了
payment.
支付
So, I get a confirmation in
所以我在 SafariViewController
Safari View Controller.
上得到了确认
This is new to iOS 11.
这是 iOS 11 的新功能
Now I'd like to talk about some
接下来 就是有关于
privacy improvements on iOS 11
iOS 11 版的 SafariViewController
in Safari View Controller.
关于隐私的升级
Browsing the web in your app is
在你自己的 App 中浏览网页
different than browsing the web
和你在其他 App 中浏览
in other apps.
网页是不同的
It's different than browsing the
它和在 Safari 中浏览
web in Safari.
网页也是不一样的
I sometimes want to use
有时候 我们在不同
different accounts when browsing
App 中浏览网页时
the web in different apps.
会想要使用不同的账户
For some apps, I'll use my work
比如有的 App 中 我会用我的工作
account and for other apps I'll
账户 而其他的 App
use my personal account.
我就会用我的个人账户
On iOS 11, Safari View
iOS 11 版的 SafariViewCotnroller
Controller will have a separate
都会为每个使用
persistent data store in each
它的 App 存储
app that it's used in.
独立的不变数据
This means that cookies, local
这就意味着 缓存
storage, and other browsing data
本地存储 以及其他浏览数据
will be contained within your
都专属于
app and scoped to your app.
你的 App
And this means that the user
也就意味着 用户并不会
won't automatically be logged in
自动登录到
to whatever accounts they were
任何他们在 Safari
logged into in Safari.
中登录的账户
What this does is it will
这是为了
prevent cross-app tracking of
防止跨 App 的
user's browsing activity that
用户跟踪浏览活动
you and your users may not have
而你和你的用户可能都不知道
even been aware about.
这种跟踪的存在
And ultimately, it helps keep
最终 它将会
users' browsing activity private
帮助你保证用户浏览操作的隐私性
and scoped within your app.
并把用户的浏览限制在你的 App 中
Now I'd like to talk about a
接着便是
change to Private Browsing in
SafariViewController 中
Safari View Controller.
无痕浏览模式的更新
Now that Safari View Controller
现在 SafariViewController
has its own separate persistent
已经为每个 App 存储了
data store for each app, it's
独立的不变数据
browsing mode is no longer tied
也就是它的浏览模式不再
to Safari's this means that I
与 Safari 的绑定这意味着
now longer get the following
我再也不用经历
frustrating experience.
下面这些让人崩溃的事情了
I'm browsing the web in Safari
我正在 Safari 上
in Private Mode.
用无痕模式浏览网页
Time passes and later that day
随着时间的流逝 那天晚些时候
after I've forgotten that I was
我忘了我用了
even in Private Mode, I go to my
无痕模式 并打开了我最喜欢的一个
favorite app that opens links
App 用 SafariViewController
using Safari View Controller.
打开了一个链接
Safari View Controller is
SafariViewController　打开
presented in Private Mode once I
链接的时候 自动使用了
open a link and that's confusing
无痕模式这让我觉得有点困惑
to me because I didn't
因为我并没有
intentionally tell it to open in
让它开启
Private Browsing Mode.
无痕模式
So, on iOS 11 now that Safari
现在 iOS 11 上的
View Controller has its own
SafariViewController 有自己的
browsing mode, it's no longer
浏览模式 它就不再和
tied to Safari's.
Safari 的模式绑定
That means that your apps' color
也就是你的 App 的配色
scheme will be used more often.
将会使用的更加频繁
Now I'd like to tell you about
现在 我要和你们介绍
three new APIs that we've added
三个新增的 API
so you can really tailor Safari
这三个 API 可以
View Controller to fit your
让你的 SafariViewController
app's experience.
与你的 App 风格一致
First I'd like to talk to about
首先 让我们来看看
how you can now customize the
你们现在可以对
Dismiss button of Safari View
SafariViewController 的
Controller.
Dismiss 按钮所做的修改
Language is very important when
当向用户传达信息时
conveying intent to the user.
语言是十分重要的
The standard Dismiss button
SafariViewController 的标准
style for Safari View Controller
Dimiss 按钮是
is Done.
Done
This works really well for a
这适用于标准的
standard browsing case, because
浏览用例因为
the user can browse through a
用户可以浏览
bunch of different web pages and
许多不同的网页 当
then when they're finished
他们已经完成浏览 他们就可以
browsing tap Done to indicate
单击 Done 来
that they've ended their
表示他们的浏览
browsing session.
已经结束了
On iOS 11 we've added two new
iOS 11 的
options that this Dismiss button
Dismiss　新增了
can take on.
两种选项
The first of those options is
第一个是
Cancel.
Cancel
I think Cancel makes a lot of
我认为 Cancel 这个选项
sense when I'm getting my user's
在我的用户授权
authenticated to a third-party
第三方服务时 有
service.
一定存在的意义
The user will know that if they
用户们会知道如果他们
tap that button, they're not
单击这个按钮时 他们
really authenticating with my
并没有真正授权我的
service, they're cancelling the
服务 而是取消了
transaction.
这次操作
The other new style is Close.
另外一个选项便是 Close
This makes sense if I'm
如果我在向用户展示
presenting some transient web
一些静态的网页内容
content to the user, perhaps a
比如服务条约之类的时候
Terms of Service page.
这个选项就有存在的必要
I'm giving them a page where
因为我为他们提供的网页
they're probably not likely to
并不太可能让他们
follow other links, so they'll
打开其他的链接 所以
just Close once they've finished
他们阅读完
reading what I've presented to
我所展示的东西之后就可以
them.
单击 Close
Now I'd like, or the Dismiss
Dismiss 按钮的样式
button style is a property on
是 SFSafariViewController 上
SFSafariViewController.
的一个属性
As I mentioned it has these two
我刚刚提到了它有这两个
new options.
新的选项
The default style will be Done
它的默认样式将会是 Done
but you can choose which ever
但是你可以从这两种
style best fits your use case of
样式中选择最适合
Safari View Controller.
你的 SafariViewController 的用例
The value can even be changed
甚至当 SafariViewController
while Safari View Controller is
正在使用的时候 你也
presented, which Louie will
可以更改这个数值
demonstrate later.
Louie 将稍后向我们展示这一功能
Now I'd like to talk to you
现在我将介绍一下
about a customization you can
你能对 SafariViewController
make to the Share Sheet in
上的 Share Sheet
Safari View Controller.
所做的个性化定制
Let's say I'm presenting a login
假设我现在正在向用户
flow to the user.
呈现一个登录的流程
When the tap the share button
当他们单击分享的按钮
they have all these different
他们可以执行这么多不同
actions that they can take, but
的操作 但有些操作
some of them don't really make
在这个例子里
sense in this case.
并不太需要
They're probably not going to
用户不太可能
send the page somewhere else
将这个页面发送到其他的地方
because it might disrupt the
因为这有可能会干扰
login flow and the login might
登录的流程而且这个流程
now even work outside of the
现在有可能在
context of my app.
我的 App 之外的地方运行
Here, I've filtered out, so this
我在这里做了筛选
is what the actions that I don't
这是我不想要显示的
want to show.
操作
On iOS 11 we're giving the
在 iOS 11 上 我们让 SafariViewController
ability to filter out some of
可以筛选掉一些
these UIActivityTypes.
UIAcitivityTypes
Here, I've filtered out AirDrop,
我把 AirDrop 邮件
Mail, and Messages because my
和短信筛选掉 因为我的
users don't need them in this
用户并不需要
case.
这些功能
You make recognize this API on
你可能会认出 UIActivityViewController
UIActivityViewController.
上的这个 API
It allows you to set an array of
它允许你在你的
UIActivityTypes that the user
UIActivityController 中
doesn't need on your
设置一系列用户
UIActivityViewController.
不需要的 UIActivityType
We realize that if you're
我们认为如果你们
implementing your own in-app web
打算实现你们自己的 in-app
browsing experience, you'd have
网页浏览体验的话 你们应该
the ability to customize the
要有自定义
Share Sheet in this way.
Share Sheet 的途径
So, in iOS 11 we're exposing
所以 我们将在 iOS 11
this same ability on
上的 SFSafariViewControllerDelegate 中
SFSafariViewControllerDelegate
加上这个功能
as a method where you can return
让你可以反馈一组你
an array of UIActivityTypes that
不想在你的
you don't want to be presented
SafariViewController 中
to the user in the context of
向用户展示
your Safari View Controller.
的 UIActivityTypes
Now, I'd like to talk about Bar
接下来要展示的是
Collapsing in Safari View
SafariViewController 中
Controller.
栏的折叠
Safari View Controller's bars
当用户在浏览的时候
collapse away while in browsing,
SafariViewController 的栏会折叠起来
which lets me really get
让我们专心
immersed in my browsing
浏览网页
experience.
的内容
However, in some cases this bar
但在某些情况下 栏的折叠
collapsing behavior can be
有时候会让
frustrating.
人崩溃
Let's say I have a login flow.
假设说我现在正在登录
If bars are collapsed, the
但是栏折叠起来了
Dismiss button gets hidden.
Dimiss 按钮被隐藏起来
So, it's a bit more difficult to
这样子关掉
Dismiss Safari View Controller.
SafariViewController 就有点困难了
So, in something quick like a
也就是说 针对一些流程而言
login flow, this standard bar
比如登录 栏的折叠
collapsing behavior might not
并不
necessarily make sense.
是很合适
On iOS 11, we're allowing you to
所以在 iOS 11 中 如果你们
disable this standard bar
觉得停用这个功能更
collapsing behavior if it best
符合你们的用例的话
fits your use case.
你们就可以停用它
This will be a new property on
它将会成为
SFSafariViewController
SFSafariViewController 中的一个
.Configuration which will be
新属性 并将
passed into Safari View
进入到 SafariViewController
Controller's initializer.
的初始程序中
It's best to leave this enabled
如果你的用例是为了
if your use case is show user's
让用户浏览 或者用户
browsing, or user's content that
真的需要专注于
they should really get immersed
他们的浏览内容的话 最好
in.
还是启用这个功能
But, if it's important to always
但如果保持 Dismiss
have the Dismiss button shown,
按钮时刻显示更为重要的话
you can disable this property.
你也可以停用它
Now, I'd like to welcome Louie
现在 让我们欢迎 Louie
back to the stage to show you
回到台上来为我们
how easy it is to use these new
展示使用这些新的 API
APIs to tailor for his app's
来自定义他的 App 体验
experience.
的便捷性
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Thanks, Chelsea.
&gt;&gt; 谢谢 Chelsea
I'm thrilled to show you how
能有机会向你们介绍
easy it is to customize Safari
使用新的 API
View Controller using these new
自定义 SafariViewController
APIs and I'm going to give you a
的便捷性 我感到很高兴
sneak peak at the next app I'm
我还会让你们抢先看看我正在
working on.
开发的新 App
It's another pizza related app,
这是另外一个披萨相关的 App
so I hope that's not too cheesy.
希望你们不会觉得太腻
[laughter] This is a social app
这是一个叫 Pizza Stories
called Pizza Stories.
的社交软件
It allows you to share all the
它可以帮助你将生活中与
pizza related news in your life
披萨相关的新闻以
in a visual format with your
一种可视化的格式
friends and family.
与你的朋友和家人分享
By default, it when you're not
在没有登录的状态下
logged in, you get a list of
你会默认得到一系列
pizza brands that are sharing
分享故事的
some stories.
披萨栏目
However, to get the best
不过如果想要享受到
experience out of this app,
这个 App 的最佳体验
you'll want to log-in.
你还是需要登录一下
I don't want users to have to
我不希望我的用户还需
create and maintain a list of
在我的 App 中重新创造并
their friends in my app, and I
维持新的朋友列表
don't own a social network that
但我本身并没有拥有一个
already has this, so I want them
已经拥有这种朋友列表的社交网络 所以
to be able to use an existing
我希望他们可以
list that they've already used
使用他们在现有的
and created all of their friends
社交网络中创造并使用
on an existing social network.
的朋友列表
I'm using Safari View Controller
我通过 SafariViewController
to let them log-in and
让他们登录并
authenticate against this social
授权这一
network.
社交网络
I tap Log In, Safari View
我单击登录 SafariViewController
Controller is shown and let's my
出现 并让我的用户
users log in with SampleChat a
登录 SampleChat 一个
really popular demo social
很流行的模拟
network.
社交网络
You may have noticed that Safari
你可能会留意到
View Controller came in from
SafariViewController 是从
right to left like a
右到左出现 就像
UINavigationController.
UINavigationController 一样
My app doesn't use this
我的 App 并没有使用这种
paradigm, so that feels a little
样式 所以看起来
weird.
有一点奇怪
I have already made it so that
我已经让
Safari View Controller takes on
SafariViewController 使用我
the colors of my app, but the
App 的颜色 但是这个
transition didn't feel right for
过渡在我的 App 上
my app.
看起来有些不自然
Similarly, saying Done doesn't
同样的 Done 这个按钮
really make sense here.
在这里也不合适
I want to communicate to my
我想告诉我的用户的是
users that tapping this button
点击这个按钮
will cancel this login session.
可以取消登录
So, it's clear what's going to
这样子他们就清楚地知道
happen when they tap it.
当他们点这个按钮时会发生什么
And if my users are reading the
如果我的用户正在阅读
Terms of Service and they scroll
服务条约 并向下进行了
down a little bit, the bars
翻阅 栏会
collapse.
折叠起来
This might nice in some other
栏的折叠在某些情况下会是
web pages, but here it could
一个很好的功能 但是在这里会
just get annoying.
让人有些恼火
If they want to cancel, it's two
他们如果想要取消
taps away instead of one.
需要点击两下而不是一下
So, I'll show you how to improve
接下来 我将会向你们展示
Safari View Controller to fit
如何让 SafariViewController
this log in a little bit better.
更好的适应这一登录流程
Here's where I'm presenting
这里是我展示
Safari View Controller.
SafariViewController的地方
Like before, it's pretty simple.
和之前一样 它看起来很简单
I'm creating a URL and then
我正在创造一个 URL
passing that to Safari View
并将它放到 SafariViewController
Controller's initializer.
的初始程序中
Customizing the colors as I
将颜色定义成我之前
showed you before.
展示的颜色
And then presenting Safari View
接下来便要呈现
Controller.
SafariViewController
But let's make some changes.
但是让我们做一些改变
First, let's make sure that the
首先 让我们确保
bars don't collapse when they
当用户向下浏览时 栏
scroll down.
不会折叠
So, what I've done here is
我在这里所做的就是
created a Safari View Controller
创造一个 SafariViewController
configuration object and then
的配置对象并将它的
set its barCollapsingEnabled
barCollapsingEnabled 的属性设为
property to false.
false
This way when they scroll down
这样 当他们向下滚动时
the bars won't collapse, they'll
栏不会折叠起来 而是
still stay full height.
保持原来的高度
I then pass this in to Safari
我把这个放到
View Controller's initializer.
SafariViewController 的初始程序中
Let's make a couple other
接下来 让我来做
changes.
一些其他的改变
I've done two different things
我在这里做了两个
here.
改变
The first, is setting
第一个便是将 dismissButtonStyle
dismissButtonStyle to Cancel so
改为 Cancel
that the button will say Cancel
让按钮显示 Cancel
instead of Done, which is the
而不是默认的
default.
Done
Second change I've made is
我所做的第二个改变
slightly more complicated.
会比第一个要复杂一点
I'm overriding the
我用我的 Self 覆盖了
transitioningDelegate of Safari
SafariViewController 的
View Controller to myself.
transitioningDelegate
Since I haven't implemented any
因为我还没有应用任何
of the methods of
形式的 UITransitioningDelegate
UITransitioningDelegate, I'm
我将会使用
just going to get the standard
系统的默认
system default behavior where a
模式 界面将
view comes in from bottom to
从下至上
top.
呈现出来
I'll rebuild and show you how
我将会重建并向你们展示
this works in Pizza Stories.
这些如何在 Pizza Stories 上运行的
Now when I tap Log In, Safari
现在 我单击登录
View Controller came in from
SafariViewController 从下至
bottom to top.
上呈现出来
Now you may notice here, the
你可能会注意到这个
view is blank.
界面是空白的
This is a bug on Seed 1.
这是 Seed 1 上的一个 bug
If you do run into this, I'll
如果你真的遇到了这个问题
show you how to fix it.
我会告诉你怎么解决它
You can either pull down
你可以下拉
Notification Center or press the
通知中心或者按压 Home 键
Home button and then go back in
然后再回到页面
and the page loads.
你会发现页面已经被成功加载
So, in addition to the new
除了新的
presentation, the Dismiss button
呈现方式之外 Dimiss 按钮
says Cancel to better indicate
的文字改为 Cancel 来向我的
to my users what tapping this
用户解释单击
will do.
这个按钮的功能
And when I scroll down, the bars
当我向下滑动时 栏
don't squish.
并没有折叠
So, we're almost there.
这样子就差不多了
However, there's one more change
但是我还想多做一个
I want to make.
改变
Right now, it makes sense for
Dimiss 按钮现在显示
the button to say Cancel.
Cancel 是没有问题的
But, when my users successfully
但是 当我的用户成功
logged in, it shouldn't say
登录之后 它不应该还是显示
Cancel.
Cancel
I want to indicate to them that
我想让他们知道
it's okay to dismiss after that.
在登录之后 dismiss 是可以的
So, as Chelsea mentioned before,
就像 Chelsae 刚刚所提到的
what's really cool about this
这个属性真正酷炫的一点在于
property is it can be changed
就算我已经展示了
even after I've already
SafariViewController 我还是
presented Safari View
可以对它
Controller.
进行修改
When my user logs in with
当我的用户通过 SampleChat
SampleChat, they redirect to a
登录之后 他们将被重定向
URL scheme that my app handles.
到一个由我的 App 处理的 URL Scheme
That gets handled in my
它们将会通过这种
AppDelegate in this method.
方式在我的 AppDelegate 中得到处理
And what I'm doing here is I'm
我在这里所做的就是
making sure that there's a log
确保他有一个登录
in token to indicate that the
的 token 来表示
user's authenticated, then I'm
用户已经授权了 然后我将
sending a message to elsewhere
向我的 App 中的其他位置
in my app giving it that token.
发送这个 token 信息
I'm handling that here.
我会在这里进行操作
And I'm doing that because I
我之所以这样操作是因为
like to keep this code
我喜欢保持代码的
organized.
有序性
I want everything related to
我希望所有和登录有关的东西
Login in one place rather than
都放在一个地方 而不是
having it in a few different
分布在不同
places.
的地方
Now that I know that the user
现在我知道用户已经
has successfully logged in, I
成功登录了 我就把
can change the
SafariViewController 的
dismissButtonStyle of Safari
DimissonButoonStyle
View Controller to Done instead
从 Cancel 改为
of Cancel.
Done
So, I'll rebuild and I'll show
我重建一下 并让你们看看
you how this all comes together
这些是如何在 Pizza Stories
in Pizza Stories.
上运行的
Now, when I tap Log In, Safari
当我单击登录时
View Controller is still
SafariViewController 还是从
presented from bottom to top and
下到上出现 而
the button initially does say
这个按钮也显示的是
Cancel.
Cancel
With just a couple taps I can
我只要轻点几下
use AutoFill to log in.
就可以用 AutoFill 来登录
Now, SampleChat is asking the
SampleChat 现在正在询问用户
user if they want to allow this
是否允许这个 App
app, in this case Pizza Stories,
也就是 Pizza Stories
to use their account for their
通过他们的账号获得
friends list and their email.
他们的朋友列表和邮件
I'll allow that.
我选择了同意
And now that I'm logged in, the
现在我已经成功登录了
Done button, the Dismiss button
Dismiss 按钮也就变成了
has changed to say Done to
Done 来告诉我的用户
better indicate to my users it's
现在可以关闭
okay to dismiss now.
页面了
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
Thanks. So, when I dismiss, now
谢谢 所以当我关闭之后
I get all of my friends showing
我可以看到我的朋友们
up in my, and I can see all
出现在我的列表中 我
their stories.
可以看到他们的所有故事
This might make me crave some
这可能会使
pizza later on though.
我吃披萨的愿望有所推迟
Thanks, and this is how easy it
谢谢大家这就是使用新的
is to customize Safari View
API 自定义
Controller using the new APIs in
iOS 11 版 SafariViewController
iOS 11 to tailor it to your app
使它更符合你的 App
and make a great log in
并提供更好的登录体验
experience.
的便捷性
Thank you so much and I'll hand
谢谢大家 接下来
it back over to Chelsea.
让我们有请 Chelsea
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Thanks, Louie.
&gt;&gt; 谢谢 Louie
I think Louie is going to making
我想 Louie 这个 App
a lot of dough off that one.
应该可以赚很多钱
[laughter] Louie just showed you
Louie 刚刚向你们展示了
how with a few key improvements,
他如何通过几个重要的
he made, he took his log in flow
更新 用 SafariViewController
with Safari View Controller to
使他的登录流程
the next level.
上升一个层次
He did this by using a custom
他通过一个个性化的呈现方式
presentation style that it felt
使 SafariViewController
more like the presentation style
变得更像他 App 的
in his app.
风格
He changed the Dismiss button to
他将 Dimiss 按钮改为 Cancel
say Cancel so that users know
来让他的用户知道
that if they tap that button
如果他们点击这个按钮
they'll be cancelling log in
他们将会取消
with the third-party service
登录 Louie 要求他们
he's asking them to log in with.
登录的第三方服务
He turned off bar collapsing.
他关闭了栏折叠
This way if the user reads the
一旦用户阅读了
Terms of Service and decides
服务条约之后
that they don't want to use that
觉得他们不想使用这个服务了
service, they can quickly tap
他们可以通过单击 Cancel
cancel to exit Safari View
来快速退出
Controller.
SafariViewController
And he changed the button to say
同时 一旦用户
Done once the user had allowed
授权了第三方服务
access to that third-party
就把按钮
service.
改为 Done
This way they know that they've
这样用户就知道他们
finished logging in.
已经完成登录了
One of the main things that we
通过这个展示我们想
want you to get out of this
让你知道的是
presentation is that we hear
我们在
you.
努力倾听
The new APIs that we've talked
我们今天所提及的新的 API
about today were inspired by
都是以你们的反馈
feedback from you.
作为灵感源泉而得来的
We really encourage you to keep
我们鼓励你们继续
giving us feature requests and
向我们提出功能方面的需求并
filing bug reports.
填写 bug 报告
And also letting us know if
同时 让我们知道
there are any other
你们是否有其他希望
customizations you'd like to see
能在 SafariViewController 上
in Safari View Controller.
看到的自定义内容
So, keep talking to us.
请一直和我们沟通
In summary, Safari View
总的来说 SafariViewController
Controller gives you an easy
为你提供了一种
in-app web browsing experience.
简单的 in-app 浏览体验
With just a couple lines of
只需要几行代码
code, you can get Safari View
你就可以让
Controller up and running in
SafariViewController 在你
your app.
的 App 中运行
Safari View Controller is
SafariViewController 是
perfect for authenticating with
第三方授权的完美方式
third-party services because it
因为它既有用户所
provides a security that users
需要的安全性 也
need and the features that they
提供了他们在登录时
love while getting logged in.
所喜欢的功能
There are many improvements to
iOS 11 版的 SafariViewController
Safari View Controller on iOS
有着许多
11.
的提升
Safari View Controller's new
SafariViewController 的新外观和
look and the new APIs that we've
我们所介绍的新 API 能够
introduced can help Safari View
让 SafariViewController
Controller feel at home in your
和你的 App 无缝
app.
契合
If you've taken a look at Safari
如果你过去曾经尝试过
View Controller in the past but
SafariViewController 但觉得
maybe it didn't quite fit your
它并不是十分符合你的用例
use case, we encourage you to
我们建议你再
take another look.
给它一次机会
These improvements on iOS 11 and
iOS 11 版所做的升级 和新
the APIs that have been added
增加的 API
were inspired by you.
都是因你们而生
So, we really hope there's
所以我们衷心希望
something in there for you.
你们能找到你们想要的东西
For more information on this
关于这次研讨会的更多信息
session you can view the page
你们可以浏览
listed here.
这个网页
I'd like to tell you about some
我想向你们介绍一些
related sessions that you might
相关的 你们可能会感兴趣的
be interested in.
的研讨会
These are all available on the
它们在 WWDC 的网站和 App
WWDC website and app.
上都可以观看
We've talked a lot about getting
我们讨论了很多关于
your user authenticated with a
如何用 SafariViewController
third-party service using Safari
让你们的用户授权
View Controller.
第三方服务
But if you want to make
但是如果你想授权
authenticating with your own
你自己的服务 为你
service a better experience for
的用户提供更好的
your users you can watch
体验 你可以看看
Introducing Password AutoFill
App 中密码自动
for Apps.
填充的介绍
If you want to learn about new
如果你想了解
APIs in WKWebView, you can watch
WKWebView 的新 API 你可以
Customize Loading in WKWebView.
观看 WKWebView 的自定义加载
And to see more background on
如果你想了解更多
Safari View Controller you can
SafariViewController 的背景
watch Introducing Safari View
你可以观看 2015 年 WWDC
Controller from WWDC 2015.
的 SafariViewController 简介
Thank you so much.
十分感谢大家
I hope you have a great WWDC
希望你们能够好好享受 2017 年的
2017.
WWDC